thepoortraveler.net 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use | The Poor Traveler Itinerary Blog

**WanderGeneration.com**  is a network of blogs, including The Poor Traveler and PhilippineBeaches.org, that publish articles about a wide range of topics created by our team or submitted to us by various contributors. The network or any of the blogs, from hereon referred to as WanderGeneration collectively or individually, is  **NOT**  a travel agency, tour operator, airline, resort, or hotel.

These  **Terms of Use**  govern your use of this website and other blogs under WanderGeneration. If you do not agree with any of these Terms, please hit the exit button now and do not use any information posted. Please read carefully.

  1. By using WanderGeneration.com, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms effective on your first use of this site. If you do not agree to any of these Terms, please leave this website and do not access, contribute to, and/or use any of the information posted here.
  2. All copyright, trade marks, and other intellectual property rights (registered and unregistered) in and on WanderGeneration and its content remain with WanderGeneration or its licensors (including contributors), unless otherwise stated. Any of these may not be reproduced, duplicated, posted, stored electronically or archived except for personal non-public use without WanderGeneration’s and/or the contributor’s expressed written consent.
  3. If you own one or more pictures, text or other materials posted on this site and you want them taken down, please let us know and we will gladly cooperate.
  4. You agree that WanderGeneration may make changes to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy at any time without notice. You accept that it is your responsibility to check or review these Terms for such revisions or changes. Your continued use of the blogs/sites after changes are made to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Terms of Use and Privacy Policy

  1. You accept that WanderGeneration is a blog that features accommodations, tours, and other travel products offered by a third party Supplier (referred to hereon as “Supplier”), which may be a travel agency, tour operator, hotel, airline, cruise company, among others.
  2. You accept that it is your responsibility to familiarize yourself with the rules, restrictions, terms, and conditions of the Supplier before making a reservation or booking. It is essential that you read and understand their terms.
  3. You accept that WanderGeneration is only a publishing channel and is NOT a travel agency or tour operator. You accept that we only serve as an interface between you and the Supplier. You waive, release, indemnify, hold harmless, and discharge WanderGeneration and its staff from any and all liability, claims, demands, actions, rights of actions, or legal proceedings whatsoever, whether personal to you or to a third party should you encounter any untoward incident due to participation in the tour. You accept that complaints and other concerns about the tour are between you and the Supplier only.
  4. You declare that you are of legal age and are legally authorized to enter contractual obligations and have the authority or consent to act on behalf of the persons included in your reservation or booking. You understand that minors joining the tour must be accompanied by an adult.
  5. You agree that you are responsible for the information you provide during the reservation or booking process. You guarantee that the information you provide is truthful and accurate.
  6. You understand that the number of slots is limited and may change at any time.
  7. You understand that before a tour is reserved or book, you must accomplish our reservation form and agree to these Terms. Submitting an accomplished form does not mean completion of the reservation process, but only a registration of interest to join the tour. You understand that a WanderGeneration or Supplier staff will be contacting you to confirm that your reservation request has been received.
  8. You accept that you must settle the reservation fee by depositing it to the account of the supplier and send a copy of the deposit slip to the email address provided by WanderGeneration or the Supplier to complete your reservation. Once received, WanderGeneration or the Supplier will confirm receipt of the deposit. Until then, no reservation is final.
  9. You understand that we can only hold your reservation for 5 days since you submit the reservation form or until 5 days before the travel date, whichever is earlier. WanderGeneration and Supplier reserve the right to cancel your reservation if payment is not received in a timely fashion.
  10. You accept that the reservation fee is non-refundable but is transferrable to another person.
  11. You accept that changes in booking must be done at least 7 days before the travel date.
  12. You accept that WanderGeneration and Supplier reserve the right to refuse service to minors traveling alone and customers with a record of disregarding safety, becoming abusive, or inflicting damage to the environment in previous trips.

  1. You agree that the content you submit may or will be published on this blog or corresponding social media accounts; and may be edited to fit our editorial standards.
  2. You declare that you have the full legal right and authority to grant this website and social media accounts the right to use your content.
  3. You grant this blog license to repost or feature the submitted content on the site and partner sites, pages and accounts without making payment to you or any third party.  **You will be given full credit as the owner of the content.**
  4. You guarantee that the content you submit does not infringe upon or violate the right of privacy or right of publicity of, violate any copyright or intellectual property right, or constitute a slander or libel against, or violate any common law or any other right of, any person or entity.
  5. You are solely responsible for the content you submit. You waive, indemnify, release, and discharge WanderGeneration and its staff from any and all liability, claims, actions, or legal proceedings whatsoever, whether personal to you or to a third party should you encounter any untoward incident due to participation in this blog.
  6. You agree that this blog reserve the right to reject or remove your post at any time without notice.
  7. The following are strictly prohibited in this site.  
a. Visual or verbal profanities  
b. Nudity and sexually explicit or suggestive acts  
c. Graphic display of violence or child abuse  
d. Content that you do not own or do not have full legal right to allow PhilippineBeaches.org or its partner sites, pages or other online accounts to use.  **Please do not submit content that is not yours.**

  1. Although we do our best to keep the content of our blogs updated, you accept that it is your responsibility to double check the accuracy, feasibility or timeliness of the information directly with the concerned establishment, authority, or organization (e.g. government, immigration department, tourism board, airline, hotel, application, brand, website)
  2. You acknowledge that WanderGeneration cannot always verify if the information posted on this website including travel and tour packages and other products and services are legitimate, legal, accurate or even existent. Please practice caution when dealing with ad-owners, especially when sending money, and going on trips.
  3. You accept that WanderGeneration is not responsible for your safety.
  4. You accept that WanderGeneration is monetized and is earning through ads, sponsored content, affiliate links and other means, through visits, leads, and conversions among others.
  5. You waive, release, indemnify, hold harmless, and discharge WanderGeneration and its staff from any and all liability, claims, demands, actions, rights of actions, or legal proceedings whatsoever, whether personal to you or to a third party should you encounter any untoward incident due to participation in this site.
  6. You accept that the information, images and other materials posted on ad entries were sent in by travel agencies, resorts, airlines or hotels. You accept that we cannot verify that such materials are legally owned by those who submit them to us.
  7. You are solely responsible for any content or information you publish.
  8. You agree that WanderGeneration and its partner sites, pages and accounts reserve the right to remove your post at any time without notice.
  9. The following are strictly prohibited in this site.  
a. Visual or verbal profanities  
b. Complete or partial nudity and sexually explicit or suggestive acts  
c. Graphic display of violence or child abuse  
d. Trolling or flame-baiting  
e. Double-posting or flooding  
f. Content that you do not own or do not have full legal right to allow WanderGeneration or its partner sites, pages or other online accounts to use.  **Please do not post content that is not yours.**

This section explains our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of  
Personal Information we receive from users of our sites including but not limited to WanderGeneration, PhilippineBeaches.org and The Poor Traveler.

  1. By using our blogs, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
  2. You allow us to use your Personal Information for improving, analyzing, and marketing of the sites.
  3. While using our Site, you accept that we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name and email address (“Personal Information”).
  4. You acknowledge that like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our blogs (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, device type, the pages of our blogs that you visit, the time and date of your visit, visit duration, and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services including but not limited to Google Analytics and Sumo plugin.
  5. You accept that we may use your Personal Information to send you newsletters, analyze traffic, or support our marketing or promotional efforts like polls.
  6. You accept that when visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
  7. If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
  8. You accept that we use cookies to collect data. Cookies are files with data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to experience the blogs as they are originally designed.
  9. You accept that if you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
  10. You accept that articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
  11. You accept that if you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
  12. You accept that comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
  13. You agree that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

You can reach the admins by sending an email to  **yoshke (at) thepoortraveler.net**

Last updated: 24 May 2018
